Date of birth: 23.06.1996

Address: Andon Slabejko 110^b, Prilep, North Macedonia

Email: risteska i@yahoo.com
Telephone: +389 78/ 410 – 390

in www.linkedin.com/in/ivana-risteska96

Driving License: B-Category



Ivana Risteska

PERSONAL STATEMENT

Highly motivated, excellent communicator, ambitious, efficient, works well under pressure, can multitask with ease, and strives to achieve goals within the given timeframe.

Working at GENTHERM, Prilep, North Macedonia. A company that is part of Automotive industry and that investigates a broad spectrum of technologies as Automotive Cable Technologies, Cell Connecting Boards, Battery Thermal Management, Electronics, Seat Comfort & Interior Comfort.

In my role as a Supply Planner, I have a variety of responsibilities, including a variety of duties related to working with people in a team environment. Monitoring and controlling inventory level of materials, shelf life of materials in parallel with monitoring production requirements.

Over a period of 1.5 year, I have been working as a Quality Engineer where I was responsible for PPAP documentation and communicating with Customer in order to make them sure that our product is meeting their requirements through controlling the quality of it.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

09/2020 – Present

Supply Planner, GENTHERM, Prilep, North Macedonia

Main tasks:

- -Maintaining raw material delivery schedules based on the demands and providing them to suppliers
- -Monitoring production requirements
- -Managing with the Inventory level of the materials
- -Monitoring the shelf life of the materials
- -Escalations in case of not followed schedule at the supplier's side

03/2019 - 09/2020

Quality Planning Engineer, GENTHERM, Prilep, North Macedonia

Main tasks:

- -Preparing of PPAP documentation and sending to customer
- -Creating Control Plan which is needed for quality control of outputs to meet customer requirements
- -Monitoring the Inspection Plans

EDUCATION

10/2019 – 11/2021 Master's Degree

Faculty of Economics: University St. Kliment Ohridski, Bitola, North Macedonia

Direction: Electronic Business

Master thesis: "Application of Cloud Computing in Customer Relationship Management"

Title: Master of science in Economics in the field of Electronic Business

Additionally gained experience: While writing the Master thesis I was working with IT professional specialists that gave me basic knowledge of Cloud computing and it's benefits which was part of the mini - volunteering

09/2015 - 07/2019 Bachelor's Degree

Faculty of Economics: University St. Kliment Ohridski, Bitola, North Macedonia

Direction: Electronic Business

Title: Graduated Economist in the field of Electronic Business

Additionally gained experience: While studying during summer breaks every year I was volunteer in different company in which way I learned basic working tasks in: Interworks (Certificate for successfully completed semestraly project in the field of research on the expansion on European market for IT companies), NLB Bank, Komercijalna Bank, General Hospital – administration, every of them in Prilep, North Macedonia.

09/2011 - 06/2015 High School

Secondary Education: Gymnasium Mirche Acev, Prilep, North Macedonia

Direction: Mathematical

09/2003 - 06/2011 Primary School

Primary Education: Kocho Racin, Prilep, North Macedonia

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Advanced: Internet, Microsoft office (Word, Excel, Power point), Microsoft outlook, SAP ERP, Dreamweaver, Wordpress, ProModel.

Basic: SQL, Salesforce, HTML & CSS.

LICENSES & CERTIFICATIONS

Leadership and Inspiration - Prilep, North Macedonia // March 2016

Youth Policy - Budva, Montenegro // February 2018

Young Managers - Prilep (Skopska Bowery), North Macedonia // February 2018

Taking initiative - Prague, Czech // June 2018

Oratorical abilities - University St. "Kliment Ohridski" Bitola, North Macedonia // March 2018

Women in Electronic Business - Skopje, North Macedonia // April 2018

Social entrepreneurship - Vinkovci, Croatia // October 2018

Two state certificates for Oratorical abilities — Bitola North Macedonia // May 2017 and May 2018

Better decisions and mediation - Krusevo, North Macedonia // November 2018

ITIL Standards, using and implementation — Prilep, North Macedonia // November 2019

MOTHER LANGUAGE

Macedonian

OTHER LANGUAGES

Familiar with the languages of former Yugoslavia Republics (Serbo-Croatian)

English – Advanced-level written and spoken

French-Basic level written and spoken

PERSONAL INTERESTS IN FREE TIME

Participating in different events (seminars, trainings & conferences) watching a good movie, reading books, city coffee breaks, summer holidays and visiting new places.

SKILLS

Efficient

Details Oriented

Multitasking

Analytical

Innovative